一个被使用最多的安卓暗示指令是
One of the most used implicit intents
是分享指令  这个指令
in Android is the share intent. It's [LAUGH]
很棒  这是一个你和你朋友
awesome. It's a great way to waste time
用来消磨时间的一个很好的方式
for both you and your friends. [SOUND] [LAUGH].
丹
>> Dan!
您能使用你最喜欢的应用去分享相片  文件
>> You can leverage your favorite apps to share photos, texts,
视频和普通链接  而这最优势的部分就是你甚至无需
videos and general links. And the best part is you don't have
知道使用者最喜欢的应用是什么  仅需要告知
to even know what the user's favorite apps are. Just tell
你想要分享的Android的什么数据然后显示你的使用者
Android what data you want to share and it shows your users
一系列应用来分享它  当你在写的
a list of apps that will share it. Apps that
应用它可能都不需要出现  为了
may not have existed when you app was written. To
使它能够更好地在安卓4.0上实现分享
make it even easier to share Android 4.0 added the
添加一个分享行为提示  我们让它成为一个安卓的
share action provider and we have it for previous releases of
优先显示的开放支持部分  使用发送
Android as part of a support library. It operates using
指令就可以实现这个行为
the action send intent.
只要你使用发送  地址就会被发送给任何你想要发送的人
it would be addressed to anyone who could perform action
数据下降包含额外的像
send. The data descend would be included with it as extras
文本或者二进制数据的网址
either as text, or URI to the binary data. And
MIME类型会指明网址的指向
the MIME type would indicate what the URI points to.
这就是分享行为提示所带给
Here's what the share action provider will bring to
我们的应用  光荣接线框  当我们
our app: the glorious wire frame. There will be
点击有提示作用的潜在的分享行为时
an additional icon in the action bar which will
在行为集合棒会有一个额外的菜单跳下来
drop down a menu when clicked to reveal potential
包含有最近分享的应用将会被
share actions. Another icon will be added to the
添加进来并分享
right of this one that contains the last application
从而添加一个分析行为提示到含详细行为的片段中去
shared to. Add a ShareActionProvider to the fragment within
在接着的格式里面分享天气
DetailActivity. It will share weather in the following format.
是的  这就是我们传递进去的查看字符串#Sunshine应用
Yes, it's just the string we passed into the view plus #SunshineApp.